hello friend welcome to simple trade
this is fuel initial we are not
recommending an instructor by ourselves
today number of stockings is six
check number one
infrastructure limited share price 350
Book value 97 5220 414 52 week long 236
visually rupees 10 market cap micro cap
stocks free to 1 is to toe face value
changes from 10 Rupees to 5 rupees one
share split into 5 2 Share foreign
let's see the fundamental of the stocks
the last one year the stock given
negative return minus 7.03 percent
negative return the stock given in the
last one year financially the company
making good profit every year the
profits are increasing
shareholding pattern almost 74.11
promoter holding very good promoter
holding Fai is holding 0.10 percent
retail and others 25.79 percent
yes
dividend history the stock given good
dividend last year they gave the stock
given three rupees dividend this year
already won rupees the company is given
the dividend
stock number two
green Crest Financial Service limited
share price 16 rupees 51 paise Book
value 14 rupees 52 week high 16 rupees
51 52 week Low 4 rupees facility rupees
10 market cap micro cap penny stocks are
stock speed one is to 10 face value
changes from 10 Rupees to 1 rupees
one chance fit into 10 share recorded 12
October it's date maybe 11 October
let's see the fundamental of the stock
last one year the star given 228 percent
return that is very huge return from the
stock
on the last one year
if we see the one or one month return
the one month return is almost 45.20
percent that is also very good but the
company is irritated I think the upper
circuit is going on this stock that's
why the graph of the company is looking
like a staircase so it is very risky
stock please note that
profit making Company the company making
every year profit
shareholding pattern almost for motor
holding is 1.25 percent that is nothing
like Bill holding for for motor holding
1.25 promoter holding return on the
others 98.75 percent
promoter welding is very poor
let's see the third stock
GPT infra project limited last one year
the stock return given return is 38.42
percent return the stock given GPT infra
project Limited
Financial the company given
profit making company
every other company properties are
increasing promoter holding almost 75
percent promoter holding mutual fund
2.37 percent FIS 0.09 percent retailer
the others 22.5 per person most of the
promoter Holdings are pledged that is a
minus point in this talk during history
the company has a good dividend history
GPT infra project limited share price is
115 52 week high 131 52 week low 67
rupees facility rupees 10 market cap
micro cab bonus one is to one one bonus
share for everyone
[Music]
and bonus
please note may consider there is no any
guarantee most of the case they will
declare number India limited share price
560 physically
52 weeks 654 52 week long 482 feasible
rupees one
market cap large cap board meeting
scheduled to be held on 26 October may
consider interim dividend also declaring
Financial result
mother sends to me wiring India limited
share price 84 52 week 94 rupees 52 week
low 56 rupees Festival rupees one market
cap mid cap board meeting scheduled to
be held on 30 September may consider
issue of bonus
ICICI lumbar General Insurance Company
Limited share 558 52 week high 6
677 52 week low 1000
78 visually rupees 10 market cap large
scam board meeting scheduled to be held
on 18 October may consider interim
dividend also declaring Financial result
if they declare interim dividend
recorded will be 28 October
thanks for watching